Hello friends, welcome to the Investment Information
YouTube channel
.  So friends, in today's video,
we will talk about the latest updates and
latest news of Multiple Share.  So let's
start the video, first of all let's
talk about Dynamatic Technologies Limited.
Friends, Dynamatic Technologies
share jumps after securing Falcon
6X Fuzz Lease manufacturing
contract. Let's understand the update in detail.
Friends, Dynamatic
Technologies Limited has expanded its
partnership with Dassault Aviation
.
This agreement has been made for the manufacture and assembly of the complete rear fuselage of Dassault's latest business jet, the Falcon Six X,
and this update has brought the
company Dynamatic Technologies Limited
into focus.  Let's now look at
HFCL Limited.  So friends,
HFCL wins Rs 656
crore export orders for optical fiber
cables, so let's understand the update in detail
.  So friends, the company HFCL Limited has
received export orders for supplying optical fiber cables worth
72.96 million US dollars, which is
Rs 656.10 crore in our Indian currency, and due to this update, the
company HFCL Limited has come into focus.
Now let's look
at Matrimony.com Limited and friends,
you can see the timing of this update here. This update has come on
December 8, 2025, which means this morning at
around 9:00 am. Friends, the
company Matrimony.com Limited has
organized a board meeting.
On December 15, 2025, and friends, this company
Matrimony.com Limited is going to
announce a buyback on December 15, 2025,
so friends, Matrimony.com
Limited
will be in focus on December 15, 2025, and because of this update,
friends, this company was in focus today. Let's
talk about Landmark Cars Limited.
Friends, Landmark Cars
Expands BYD Showroom in Pune, so let's
understand the update in detail.  So
friends, the
company Landmark Cars Limited has received approval from
BYD India to open a showroom and workshop in Pune, Maharashtra,
and friends, due to this update, the
company Landmark Cars Limited has also
come into focus due to this update.  Now let
's talk about ICICI Lombard.
Friends, ICICI Lombard Vastu
Housing Finance joins hands for
insurance distribution. So let's
understand the update in detail.  So friends,
ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company
Limited has announced a partnership with Vastu Housing Finance
and
friends, under this partnership,
insurance products will be
offered to Vastu Housing loan customers in India in 340 districts and 17 states who are loan customers of Vastu Housing Finance and friends, due to this
update, ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company Limited has
come into focus.  Now let's look at
Cochin Shipyard Limited.
Friends, Cochin Shipyard signs
contract with Sweetzer for four fully
electric transfer vessels.
Let's understand the update in detail.
Defense company Cochin Shipyard Limited has
signed a contract with Denmark-based company Sweetzer to construct four fully
electric
transfer vessels.
Friends, there are
also options for four more vessels. Friends,
this order
is a significant classified order, which means that the
value of the order is up to Rs. 500 crore.
Friends, due to this update, Cochin
Shipyard Limited has also come into focus
.  Let's look at NBCC India Limited.
Friends, NBCC India sells
175 residential units in Greater Noida for an
option worth Rs 85 crore. So let's
understand the update in detail.  PSU
company NBCC India Limited has
sold 175 residential units
with a total sales value of
approximately
Rs 485.41 crore and friends, due to this update,
NBCC India Limited has
also come into focus. Now let's
talk about Adani Group's giant company
Adani Green Energy Limited.
Friends, Adani Green Adopts TN FD
Framework Shifts Towards Nature Positive
Renewable Energy Development. Friends,
Adani Green Energy Limited is going to adopt the TN
FD Framework i.e. Task Force on
Nature Related Financial Disclosure
Framework and Adani
Green Energy Limited is going to shift towards nature
positive renewable energy
development.
Friends, due to this
update, Adani Green Energy Limited is
also going to come into focus.  So now let's
talk about Bajaj Finserv Limited,
friends, Bajaj Fin Plans foray into
Pension Wealth Management in 2026. So let's
understand the update in detail.
So friends, next year, i.e.
in the calendar year 2026, Bajaj Finanser Limited will be
entering the pension and wealth management business.  In order to increase its business
in finance, friends, Bajaj
Finsor Limited has a target of
listing its insurance subsidiary in the next four to five years.
And
not only that, friends, Bajaj Finsor
Limited has a target of
tripling its revenue by the financial year 2000-30. And
friends, due to this update, Bajaj Finsor
Limited has also come into focus
.  So friends, I hope
you found today's video informative
.  So friends, if you found this
video informative, then
like this video and subscribe to the channel.
Friends, today's video is
made only for educational purposes.
I do not have any recommendation from you whether
you should buy, sell
or hold these stocks. So let's meet in the next
video. Until then, Tata, bye bye.